Guide to the Duke University Union Records, 1954-ongoing UA.09.13.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- General Records1954-ongoing, 54 boxes
  - Special Events Committee: Vandales, March 16, 1978 (Box 14)
  - Performing Arts Committee: "Bubbling Brown Sugar", March 19, 1978 (Box 14)
  - Special Events Committee: Springfest, April 14, 1978 (Box 14)
  - Special Events Committee: The Mike Cross Show, April 19, 1978 (Box 14)
  - Performing Arts Committee: William Windom in Thurber II, 1977-1978 (Box 14)
  - Performing Arts Committee: Triangle Dance Guild, 1977-1978 (Box 14)
  - Performing Arts Committee: Finance, 1977-1978 (Box 14)
  - Performing Arts Committee Miscellaneous Records, 1967-1978 (Box 14)
  - Finance: Budget, 1977-1978 (Box 14)
  - Student Organizations, 1977-1978 (Box 14)
  - Special Events Committee: Yancy (Summer Programming), 1978 (Box 14)
  - Special Events Committee: Surveyor (Summer Programming), 1978 (Box 14)
  - Special Events Committee: Boney Maroney Band (Summer Programming), 1978 (Box 14)
  - Special Events Committee: Hickory Hollow (Summer Programming), 1978 (Box 14)
  - Current SPUD (Student Project for University Development), 1976-1978 (Box 14)
  - Craft Center Administration, 1976-1978 (Box 14)
  - Graphic Arts Committee: Budget and Operations Information, 1977-1978 (Box 14)
  - Graphic Arts Committee: Judi Bradford, July-September 1977 (Box 14)
  - Graphic Arts Committee: Helen M. Jendall, September-October 1977 (Box 14)
  - Graphic Arts Committee: Elizabeth Lyon, October-November 1977 (Box 14)
  - Graphic Arts Committee: Alex Harris, October, 1977 (Box 14)
  - Graphic Arts Committee: Ruth Pinnell, November-December 1977 (Box 14)
  - Graphic Arts Committee: Lawrence Fane, January-February 1978 (Box 14)
  - Graphic Arts Committee: Edward Gomez, February-March 1978 (Box 14)
  - Graphic Arts Committee: Student Art Show, February-March 1978 (Box 14)
  - Graphic Arts Committee: Duke Faculty Show, April-May 1978 (Box 14)
  - Graphic Arts Committee: Victor Lucas, March 24-April 18, 1978 (Box 14)
  - Programming Council: Minutes, 1977-1978 (Box 14)
  - Cameron Indoor Stadium: Reservations, 1977-1978 (Box 14)
  - University Union: Finance Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 14)
  - Performing Arts Committee: Bob Hope, 1977 (Box 14)
  - Performing Arts Committee: Budget, 1977-1978 (Box 14)
  - Spring 1978 Survey on Programming, 1977-1978 (Box 14)
  - Cable 13: Jed Daly Correspondence, 1977 (Box 14)
  - Cable 13: Development, 1977 (Box 14)
  - Cable 13: DUAA Loan, 1977 (Box 14)
  - Cable 13: Durham Cablevision, 1977 (Box 14)
  - Cable 13: Equipment (WTVD), 1977 (Box 14)
  - Cable 13: Fount, 1977 (Box 14)
  - Cable 13: Hospital Connection, 1977 (Box 14)
  - Cable 13: Legal Services, 1977 (Box 14)
  - Cable 13: Frey/Daly, 1977 (Box 14)
  - Cable 13: National Association of Broadcasters Convention, 1977 (Box 14)
  - Cable 13: Colby Report, 1977 (Box 14)
  - Cable 13: Cameron Indoor Stadium (Wiring), 1977 (Box 14)
  - Cable 13: Bull City Video, 1977 (Box 14)
  - Cable 13: Grants, 1977 (Box 14)
  - Cable 13: Production Training Program, 1977 (Box 14)
  - Cable 13: Referenda, 1977 (Box 14)
  - Cable 13: Tel-Com Head-in Systems, 1977 (Box 14)
  - Cable 13: Perkins Library, 1977 (Box 14)
  - Cable 13: Grant Proposals, 1977 (Box 14)
  - Galleries Committee: Insurance Coverage of Art Exhibits, 1977 (Box 14)
  - Galleries Committee: Gallery Lanzberg, 1977-1980 (Box 14)
  - Arts Committee: Miscellaneous Records, 1977 (Box 14)
  - Joe College, 1977 (Box 14)
  - Graphic Arts Committee: Lawrence Fane - Sculpture, circa 1977-1978 (Box 14)
  - Special Events Committee: Thursday in the Tavern "Coffeehouse"; "Melllow Construction"; Summer programming, 1978 (Box 14)
  - Cable 13: Physical Plant, 1978 (Box 14)
  - Provost Agreement: Cablevision, 1978 (Box 14)
  - Cable 13: Nightwatch, 1977-1978 (Box 44)
  - Cable 13: Public Television Library, 1976-1978 (Box 44)
  - Cable 13: Medical Center Hook-Up, 1978 (Box 44)
  - Cable 13: Outside Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 44)
  - Cable 13: Fount, 1977 (Box 44)
  - Cable 13: Cameron Indoor Stadium (Wiring), 1977 (Box 44)
  - Cable 13: Survey/Frequencies, 1977 (Box 44)
  - Cable 13: Survey/Crosstabulations, 1977 (Box 44)
  - Cable 13: Bull City Video, 1977 (Box 44)
  - Cable 13, 1978 (Box 44)
  - Cable 13: Durham Cablevision, 1977 (Box 44)
  - Cable 13: Broadcast Schedules--Fall Semester, 1977 (Box 44)
  - Cable 13: Proposals, 1978 (Box 44)
  - Cable 13: American Dance Festival, 1977-1978 (Box 44)
  - Cable 13: State Fair, 1978 (Box 44)
  - Cable 13: PPS, 1978 (Box 44)
  - Policy Manual, 1978 (Box 15)
  - NEA News, Goals, and Grants, 1977-1978 (Box 15)
  - Auditors on Boston Concert, February 13, 1977 (Box 15)
  - Programming Council: Minutes, 1977-1979 (Box 15)
  - Programmatic Staff: Minutes, 1979 (Box 15)
  - University Union: Finance, 1978-1979 (Box 15)
  - Finance, 1970-1979 (Box 15)
  - Union Events, 1978-1980 (Box 15)
  - Jan Gibson: Travel Expenses, 1978 (Box 15)
  - International Year of the Child, 1979 (Box 15)
  - Marching Band Uniforms: Stolen, 1979 (Box 15)
  - Freshman Register, 1979 (Box 15)
  - Summer Programming Committee: Programs, Summer 1977 (Box 15)
  - Final Box Office Reports: All Committees, 1978-1979 (Box 15)
  - Cable 13: Telecommunications Project, 1978 (Box 15)
  - Cable 13: Public Policy, 1978 (Box 15)
  - Cable 13: Proposals, 1978 (Box 15)
  - Cable 13: Nightwatch, 1978 (Box 15)
  - Cable 13: Membership Lists, 1978 (Box 15)
  - Cable 13: Equipment Rentals, 1978 (Box 15)
  - Cable 13: David Frey Correspondence, 1978 (Box 15)
  - Cable 13: Development Information, 1978 (Box 15)
  - Cable 13: Durham Technical Institute, 1978 (Box 15)
  - Cable 13: History, 1978 (Box 15)
  - Cable 13: "Citizen Flash", 1978 (Box 15)
  - Cable 13: Cable Project, 1978 (Box 15)
  - Galleries Committee: Mailing List Addresses, 1978-1980 (Box 15)
  - Galleries Committee: Insurance Coverage of Art Exhibits, 1978 (Box 15)
  - Miscellaneous Records, 1970s-1980s (Box 15)
  - Summer Programming: General, 1978 (Box 15)
  - NECAA National Convention, February 22-26, 1978 (Box 15)
  - Summer Programming, 1979 (Box 15)
  - Films Other than FW [Freewater] and Quad, 1970s (Box 15)
  - Budget: Interim Financial Report, 1979 (Box 15)
  - Games Room Reports, 1976-1979 (Box 15)
  - Crafts Center, 1976-1980 (Box 15)
  - Welcome Letters from the University Union President, 1976-1979 (Box 15)
  - NECAA National Convention: Washington, DC, February 13-17, 1980 (Box 15)
  - NECAA National Convention: Kansas City, MO, February 14-18, 1979 (Box 15)
  - NECAA Southeast Conference: Kansas City, MO, February, 1979 (Box 15)
  - By-Laws of Triangle Dance Guild, undated (Box 15)
  - Triangle Dance Guild: General Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 15)
  - Triangle Dance Guild, 1977-1980 (Box 15)
  - ASDU: Peripheral, 1978-1980 (Box 15)
  - ASDU, 1977-1980 (Box 15)
  - Advertising, 1977-1980 (Box 15)
  - Performing Arts Committee: The Wiz, 1978-1979 (Box 15)
  - Performing Arts Committee: The Acting Company, Preliminary Press Info, 1978-1979 (Box 15)
  - Performing Arts Committee: Ticket Manifest Sheet, 1978-1979 (Box 15)
  - Performing Arts Committee: Local Bands, Odds and Ends, 1978-1979 (Box 15)
  - Performing Arts Committee: Bill Evans, February 24, 1978 (Box 15)
  - Performing Arts Committee: California Suite, 1978 (Box 15)
  - Performing Arts Committee: Side by Side, 1978 (Box 15)
  - Performing Arts Committee: Record Bar Proposal, June, 1978 (Box 15)
  - Performing Arts Committee: Performing Arts History at Duke, 1978 (Box 15)
  - Performing Arts Committee: NC Symphony, Problems. Roberta Peters and M. Dobbs, 1978 (Box 15)
  - Performing Arts Committee: Blackstone Magic Show, 1978 (Box 15)
  - Performing Arts Committee: The Paul Taylor Dance Company and Triangle Dance Guild, 1978 (Box 15)
  - Performing Arts Committee: General Correspondence, 1978 (Box 15)
  - Performing Arts Committee: Diversions and Delights; Vincent Price as Oscar Wilde, 1978 (Box 15)
  - Performing Arts Committee: Bill Cosby, 1978 (Box 15)
  - Performing Arts Committee: Your Arms Too Short to Box with God, 1978-1979 (Box 15)
  - Performing Arts Committee: Jim Rouse, NC Showstoppers, circa 1978 (Box 15)
  - University Union: from GSA files, circa 1970s (Box 15)
  - Finance: Budget, 1978-1979 (Box 15)
  - Cable 13: Membership Lists, 1978 (Box 45)
  - Cable 13: History, 1978-1979 (Box 45)
  - Cable 13: Music Copyright Releases, 1978-1981 (Box 45)
  - Cable 13: Broadcast Schedules--Spring Semester, 1978 (Box 45)
  - Cable 13: Durham Technical Institute, 1978 (Box 45)
  - Cable 13: Catalog of Tapes, 1978 (Box 45)
  - Cable 13: David Frey Correspondence, 1978 (Box 45)
  - Cable 13: Citizen Flash, 1978 (Box 45)
  - Cable 13: Equipment Rentals, 1978 (Box 45)
  - Cable 13: South Africa Coalition, November 6, 1978 (Box 45)
  - Cable 13: Broadcast Schedules, 1978 (Box 45)
  - Cable 13: Nightwatch, 1978-1979 (Box 45)
  - Cable 13: Broadcast Schedules--Spring Semester, 1979 (Box 45)
  - Cable 13: DUAA, 1979 (Box 45)
  - Cable 13: Broadcast Schedules--Fall Semester, 1979 (Box 45)
  - Cable 13: Proposals, 1979 (Box 45)
  - Cable 13: Equipment Purchases, Apple II, 1979 (Box 45)
  - Cable 13: Facilities, 1979 (Box 45)
  - Cable 13: NASA, 1979 (Box 45)
  - Cable 13: Marching Band Uniforms, 1979 (Box 45)
  - Cable 13: Library Video Tapes, 1979 (Box 45)
  - Cable 13: Newsletters, 1979 (Box 45)
  - Cable 13: Jim Benfer Case, 1979 (Box 45)
  - Cable 13: Structure and Function, 1979 (Box 45)
  - Cable 13: Advisory Committee, 1979 (Box 45)
  - Cable 13: Newspaper Articles, 1979 (Box 45)
  - Cable 13: Medical Center Hook-Up, 1979 (Box 45)
  - Cable 13: General Information, 1979-1980 (Box 45)
  - Cable 13: Membership, 1979-1980 (Box 45)
  - Cable 13: Renovations, 010 Old Chem, 1979 (Box 45)
  - Facilities: General, 1976-1980 (Box 45)
  - Cable 13: Signed Legal Contracts, 1976-1980 (Box 45)
  - ASDU: A By-Law, undated (Box 16)
  - ASDU: Constitution/Minutes, 1979/1978-1980 (Box 16)
  - ASDU: External Affairs, 1979 (Box 16)
  - ASDU: Elections Committee, 1979 (Box 16)
  - ASDU: Monies Transferred to the Union, 1979 (Box 16)
  - Finance: Budget, 1979-1980 (Box 16)
  - Minutes, 1979-1980 (Box 16)
  - Final Box Office Reports: All Committees, 1979-1980 (Box 16)
  - Howard Wagoner Memorial, 1979-1980 (Box 16)
  - Vouchers: Letter from Tom Dixon, 1979-1980 (Box 16)
  - Jan Gibson Correspondence, circa 1978 (Box 16)
  - Galleries Committee: Marson Graphics Inc. [2 folders], 1979 (Box 16)
  - Galleries, 1979 (Box 16)
  - Galleries Committee: John Rosenthal Photographs, 1979 (Box 16)
  - Galleries Committee: Mailing Lists/Media Contacts, 1979-1980 (Box 16)
  - Galleries Committee: Past Artists, 1979-1980 (Box 16)
  - Galleries Committee: Insurance Coverage of Art Exhibits, 1979-1980 (Box 16)
  - Galleries Committee: Exhibits, 1979-1980 (Box 16)
  - Galleries Committee: Spring 1980 (Box 16)
  - Galleries Committee: "Haitian Show", circa 1979 (Box 16)
  - Galleries Committee: Exhibitions at Present, 1979-1980 (Box 16)
  - Galleries Committee: Miscellaneous Records, 1979-1980 (Box 16)
  - Galleries Committee: Former and Current Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 16)
  - Cable 13: General Information, 1979-1980 (Box 16)
  - Cable 13: Advisory Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 16)
  - Cable 13: Financial Condition, 1979 (Box 16)
  - Cable 13: Advisory Committee Letter, September 25, 1979 (Box 16)
  - Cable 13: Advisory Council Members, 1979-1980 (Box 16)
  - Cable 13: Community Television--ABC Proposal, August 29, 1979 (Box 16)
  - Cable 13: Renovations on 010 Old Chemistry, 1979 (Box 16)
  - Cable 13: Community TV--Meeting Notices, 1979-1980 (Box 16)
  - Cable 13: Budget, 1979-1980 (Box 16)
  - Cable 13: Benfer, Jim, 1979 (Box 16)
  - Cable 13: Constitution, 1979 (Box 16)
  - Cable 13: DUAA, 1979 (Box 16)
  - Cable 13: Donations, 1979 (Box 16)
  - Cable 13: Dawson, Deban, 1979 (Box 16)
  - Cable 13: Equipment Purchases, 1979 (Box 16)
  - Cable 13: Education Facilities, 1979 (Box 16)
  - Cable 13: TV Production Studio and Media Consortium, 1979 (Box 16)
  - Cable 13: Structure and Function, 1979 (Box 16)
  - Cable 13: Renovations on 010 Old Chemistry, 1979 (Box 16)
  - Cable 13: Proposals, 1979 (Box 16)
  - Cable 13: Plays - "The Best Years of Our Lives", 1979 (Box 16)
  - Cable 13: Newspaper Clippings, 1979 (Box 16)
  - Cable 13: Medical Center Hook-Up, 1979 (Box 16)
  - Cable 13: MATV, 1979 (Box 16)
  - Cable 13: Marching Band Uniforms, 1979 (Box 16)
  - Cable 13: Newsletters, 1979 (Box 16)
  - Cable 13: Library Video Tapes, 1979 (Box 16)
  - Cable 13: Community TV Financial Report, February 2, 1980 (Box 16)
  - Cable 13: "Channel 86 Newsfest"--Jim Benfer and Neal O. Williams, January 30, 1980 (Box 16)
  - Cable 13: Community TV--Taping Graduation, May 11, 1980 (Box 16)
  - Triangle Dance Guild: Board Resolution, October 17, 1979 (Box 16)
  - Triangle Dance Guild: Minutes, 1979-1980 (Box 16)
  - Triangle Dance Guild: Grant Proposal--The Washington Ballet, June 1979-May 1980 (Box 16)
  - Triangle Dance Guild, 1979 (Box 16)
  - Triangle Dance Guild: Mailing List and Donor Letter, 1979-1981 (Box 16)
  - Triangle Dance Guild: Study, 1979-1980 (Box 16)
  - Triangle Dance Guild: Securities--Sell and Endorse, October 17, 1979 (Box 16)
  - Triangle Dance Guild: Board of Directors, 1979-1980 (Box 16)
  - Graphic Arts Committee: Gwen Jensen, 1979-1980 (Box 16)
  - Graphic Arts Committee: Miscellaneous, 1979-1980 (Box 16)
  - Performing Arts Committee: Treasurer, 1979-1980 (Box 16)
  - Performing Arts Committee: Miscellaneous Records, 1979-1980 (Box 16)
  - Performing Arts Committee: Letter to Durham Schools, 1979 (Box 16)
  - Performing Arts Committee: Atlanta Ballet, 1979 (Box 16)
  - Performing Arts Committee: James Earl Jones as Paul Robeson, 1979 (Box 16)
  - Performing Arts Committee: Chicago, 1979 (Box 16)
  - Performing Arts Committee: Broadway at Duke, 1979 (Box 16)
  - Performing Arts Committee: Romeo and Juliet, The Acting Co. PA, 1979 (Box 16)
  - Performing Arts Committee: Jazz Fest, 1979 (Box 16)
  - Performing Arts Committee: The Allman Brothers and The Dixie Dregs, 1979 (Box 16)
  - Performing Arts Committee: Herbie Hancock, 1979 (Box 16)
  - Performing Arts Committee: Dan Wagoner, 1979 (Box 16)
  - Performing Arts Committee: Mike Cross Show, 1979 (Box 16)
  - Performing Arts Committee: Usher Letter, Delta Sigma Theta, 1979 (Box 16)
  - Performing Arts Committee: Miss Margarida's Way, October 14, 1979 (Box 16)
  - Performing Arts Committee: The Belle of Amherst, November 9, 1979 (Box 16)
  - Performing Arts Committee: The Gil Eagles Show, December 7, 1979 (Box 16)
  - Performing Arts Committee: Julius Caesar and Much Ado About Nothing, January 18, 1980 (Box 16)
  - Performing Arts Committee: P.S. Your Cat is Dead, February 8, 1980 (Box 16)
  - Performing Arts Committee: Ain't Misbehavin', March 23, 1980 (Box 16)
  - Performing Arts Committee: Princess Grace of Monaco, September 10, 1980 (Box 16)
  - Performing Arts Committee: The Gin Game, September 25, 1980 (Box 16)
  - Performing Arts Committee: Gertrude Stein, November 14, 1980 (Box 16)
  - Graphic Arts Committee: Holiday Craft Fair, December, 1979 (Box 16)
  - Graphic Arts Committee: Event Budget Forms, 1979-1980 (Box 16)
  - Graphic Arts Committee: Durham Arts Council, Sarah Vincent, 1979-1980 (Box 16)
  - Graphic Arts Committee: Wayne Cambern ECL, 1979-1980 (Box 16)
  - Graphic Arts Committee: Tina Guild, 1979-1980 (Box 16)
  - Budgets, 1979-1981 (Box 16)
  - Financial Summary Report, February 14, 1980 (Box 16)
  - Programming Council: Minutes, 1979-1980 (Box 16)
  - Symposium Committee: Student Symposium Committee, March 31, 1980 (Box 16)
  - Cable 13: Proposals, 1980 (Box 16)
  - Cable 13: Reynolds Foundation, 1980 (Box 16)
  - Fall Retreat/Emerald Isle, 1979-1980 (Box 16)
  - Committee on Advertising and Publicity, undated, circa late 1970s (Box 17)
  - University Union: Finances, 1976-1979 (Box 17)
  - UUB Member Lists and Minutes, 1979-1980 (Box 17)
  - Biological Sciences Building: Sound System Renovation--Room 111, 1979-1980 (Box 17)
  - Program Council Reports Fall, 1979 (Box 17)
  - Special Events Committee: Oktoberfest, 1979 (Box 17)
  - Special Events Committee: Holiday Tree Lighting, 1979 (Box 17)
  - Special Events Committee: Rainforest Plant Sale, 1979 (Box 17)
  - Special Events Committee: The Happening, 1979 (Box 17)
  - Special Events Committee: Duke University Wind Symphony, 1979 (Box 17)
  - Special Events Committee: The Stebbing Royal European Circus, 1979 (Box 17)
  - Special Events Committee: Grounds and Landscaping Conflicts, 1979 (Box 17)
  - Special Events Committee: The Mike Cross Show, 1979 (Box 17)
  - Special Events Committee: Jazz Series, 1979-1980 (Box 17)
  - Special Events Committee: Lifesaver, 1979-1980 (Box 17)
  - Special Events Committee: Yusuf Salim, 1979-1980 (Box 17)
  - Special Events Committee: The Almost 3 Mile Road Race, 1979-1980 (Box 17)
  - Special Events Committee: Springfest, 1979-1980 (Box 17)
  - Facilities, 1979 (Box 17)
  - Facilities Committee: Keys and Space Allocation, 1979-1980 (Box 17)
  - Facilities Committee: Office Spaces, 1979-1980 (Box 17)
  - University Union Board: Minutes, 1979-1980 (Box 17)
  - Baldwin Auditorium Cost Estimate, October 9, 1979 (Box 17)
  - Reunion, 1970s-1980s (Box 17)
  - Minutes, 1980 (Box 17)
  - Working Minutes, 1980 (Box 17)
  - Finance, 1980 (Box 17)
  - Financial Summary Report, 1980-1981 (Box 17)
  - DUU Newsletter, 1980 (Box 17)
  - Constitution, 1980 (Box 17)
  - Brochure: Information for Incoming Freshmen, Spring, 1980 (Box 17)
  - Brochure Letter, 1980 (Box 17)
  - Black Student Affairs, 1980 (Box 17)
  - Memos, Correspondence, 1980 (Box 17)
  - Student Committee for Institutional Advancement, 1980 (Box 17)
  - University Center Ad Hoc Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 17)
  - Facilities, 1980 (Box 17)
  - Graduate and Professional Student Council, 1980-1982 (Box 17)
  - Program Council Reports, 1980 (Box 17)
  - Residential Life Task Force Reports, 1980 (Box 17)
  - ASDU Minutes, 1980 (Box 17)
  - ASDU-General, 1980 (Box 17)
  - Duke University Union Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 17)
  - Major Attractions, 1980-1981 (Box 17)
  - "Birds in Peru": X-rated Movie, 1980 (Box 17)
  - Galleries Committee: Insurance Coverage of Art Exhibits, 1980 (Box 17)
  - Galleries Committee: Policy for Use of Galleries, 1981 (Box 17)
  - Galleries Committee: General Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 17)
  - Galleries Committee: Gary Abdullah, 1981 (Box 17)
  - Galleries Committee: Black History Month, February 1981 (Box 17)
  - Galleries Committee: Durham Arts Guild Exhibition Guidelines, 1980-1981 (Box 17)
  - Galleries Committee: Gallery Lainsberg, November 15, 1980 (Box 17)
  - Galleries Committee: Elaine Harbison, 1980 (Box 17)
  - Galleries Committee: Alan Leepa, 1981 (Box 17)
  - Galleries Committee: Thomas E. Link, June 19, 1981 (Box 17)
  - Galleries Committee: John Page, 1980 (Box 17)
  - Galleries Committee: Frank Smullen, 1981 (Box 17)
  - Galleries Committee: Unnatural Museum - East, 1980 (Box 17)
  - Galleries Committee: Miscellaneous Records, 1980-1981 (Box 17)
  - Galleries Committee: Insurance Coverage of Art Exhibits, 1981 (Box 17)
  - Galleries Committee: Photography, 1981 (Box 17)
  - Galleries Committee: Insurance for Rose Morrow, 1981 (Box 17)
  - Southern Arts Federation, circa 1980-1983 (Box 17)
  - The Rain Forest, September 16-17, 1980 (Box 17)
  - Accidents: Page Auditorium, Catherine Harris, 1980 (Box 17)
  - Union Privilege Card, 1980-1981 (Box 17)
  - Union Privilege Card: Information Letter, 1980-1981 (Box 17)
  - North Carolina Gross Receipts Tax, 1981 (Box 17)
  - Travelogs - Worldwide, 1981 (Box 17)
  - Spring Retreat, 1981 (Box 17)
  - Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 17)
  - Advertising Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 17)
  - Graduate School Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 17)
  - Programming Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 17)
  - Black History Month, 1981 (Box 17)
  - Durham County Centennial, 1981 (Box 17)
  - "Durham Centennial" play, April 29, 1981 (Box 17)
  - NECAA Southeast Regional Conference: Savannah, Georgia, October 11-14, 1980 (Box 17)
  - Cable 13: Satellite TV (SAT-FAX Steering Committee), 1981 (Box 17)
  - Cable 13: Low Power TV Handbook, 1981 (Box 17)
  - Cable 13: Advisory Committee, 1981 (Box 17)
  - Cable 13: TELESCAN (Telecommunications), 1981 (Box 17)
  - Triangle Dance Guild: Meetings, 1980-1981 (Box 17)
  - Triangle Dance Guild: Ballot New Board Members, 1980-1981 (Box 17)
  - Performing Arts Committee: Committee Personnel, 1980-1981 (Box 17)
  - Performing Arts Committee: Advertising, 1980-1981 (Box 17)
  - Performing Arts Committee: Murray Louis Dance Company, October 31, 1980 (Box 17)
  - Performing Arts Committee: The Lion in Winter, December 8, 1980 (Box 17)
  - Performing Arts Committee: Mummenschanz, January 30, 1981 (Box 17)
  - Performing Arts Committee: A Midsummer Night's Dream, March 1, 1981 (Box 17)
  - Performing Arts Committee: Les Ballets Trockadero, March 23, 1981 (Box 17)
  - Performing Arts Committee: Jacques Brel, April 10, 1981 (Box 17)
  - Performing Arts Committee: Lar-Lubivitch Dance Company, 1980-1981 (Box 17)
  - Performing Arts Committee: North Carolina Dance Theatre, 1980-1981 (Box 17)
  - Performing Arts Committee: Finance - Committed Funds, 1980-1981 (Box 17)
  - Performing Arts Committee: Progress Report - Broadway at Duke, 1980-1981 (Box 17)
  - Major Attractions, circa 1976-1981 (Box 17)
  - Programming Council: Minutes, 1980-1981 (Box 17)
  - Ad Hoc "Coordination Committee" (Programming Handbook), 1980-1982 (Box 17)
  - Miscellaneous Records, circa 1980s (Box 17)
  - Yearlook: Videotaping Graduation, 1980 (Box 17)
  - Facilities Committee: Information Desk, 1975-1980 (Box 17)
  - Special Events Committee: Bands - D.U. and CI Complete Contracts, circa 1981 (Box 17)
  - Special Events Committee: The Happening (inc. Joe Pietrantoni letter about beer), August 20, 1980 (Box 17)
  - Special Events Committee: Chris Loftis, September 12, 1980 (Box 17)
  - Special Events Committee: Hawaiian Holiday, September 17, 1980 (Box 17)
  - Special Events Committee: Road Runner Race, Fall 1980 (Box 17)
  - Special Events Committee: Oktoberfest, 1980 (Box 17)
  - Special Events Committee: Marty Bear, October 3, 1980 (Box 17)
  - Special Events Committee: Mike Cross, October 10, 1980 (Box 17)
  - Special Events Committee: Torture, October 17, 1980 (Box 17)
  - Programming for University Bars Committee: Southern Pride, October 21, 1980 (Box 17)
  - Programming for University Bars Committee: X-Teens, November 15, 1980 (Box 17)
  - Programming for University Bars Committee: Mobile City Band, November 21, 1980 (Box 17)
  - Special Events Committee: Tree Lighting, December 2, 1980 (Box 17)
  - Special Events Committee: Bands - Happened, Fall 1980 (Box 17)
  - Special Events Committee: The Pitchforks and Nothing But Treble, January 22, 1981 (Box 17)
  - Special Events Committee: Micromarathon, March 29, 1981 (Box 17)
  - Special Events Committee: Springfest, April 10, 1981 (Box 17)
  - Special Events Committee: Quad Activities, 1980-1981 (Box 17)
  - MCA/Universal Film Scholarship, 1980-1981 (Box 17)
  - Special Events: Wednesdays in the C.I., 1978 (Box 18)
  - Special Events: Disco in the C.I., 1978 (Box 18)
  - Special Events: Morton's Tapper Nickle Fire Choir (Coffee House Band), 1978 (Box 18)
  - Special Events: The Happening, "Windfall", 1978 (Box 18)
  - Special Events: The Rain Forrest Inc, Plant Show, 1978 (Box 18)
  - Special Events: Oktoberfest, 1978 (Box 18)
  - Special Events: Holiday Tree Lighting, 1978 (Box 18)
  - Special Events: Springfest, 1979 (Box 18)
  - Minutes, various committees, 1979-1980 (Box 18)
  - Cable 13: Financial, 1979-1980 (Box 18)
  - Retreat Information, 1975-1979 (Box 18)
  - Policy Minutes, 1980 (Box 18)
  - Facilities Changes, Summer 1980 (Box 18)